<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.mule.tooling.apikit.feature"
      label="APIKit Studio Plugin"
      version="1.1.0.qualifier">

   <description url="http://www.example.com/description">
      APIkit is a an Eclipse plugin for creating API definitions in
Mule Studio.
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.mulesoft.com">
      Copyright 2013 MuleSoft Inc.
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.mulesoft.com/downloads/legal/studio-license.html">
      PLEASE READ THIS BETA AGREEMENT BEFORE PURCHASING OR USING THE
PRODUCTS. BY ACCESSING OR USING THE PRODUCTS, CUSTOMER SIGNIFIES
ITS ASSENT TO THIS AGREEMENT. IF YOU ARE ACTING ON BEHALF OF
AN ENTITY, THEN YOU REPRESENT THAT YOU HAVE THE AUTHORITY TO
ENTER INTO THIS AGREEMENT ON BEHALF OF THAT ENTITY. IF CUSTOMER
DOES NOT ACCEPT THE TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT, THEN IT MUST NOT
ACCESS OR USE THE PRODUCTS.
This Beta Agreement (&apos;Agreement&apos;) is between MuleSoft, Inc. (&apos;MuleSoft&apos;)
and the purchaser or user of MuleSoft product that accepts the
terms of this Agreement (&apos;Customer&apos;). The effective date of this
Agreement (&apos;Effective Date&apos;) is the date that Customer uses MuleSoft
products.
1. Grant of License.
1.1 The License.
Subject to the terms of this Agreement, MuleSoft grants to Customer
a personal, non-exclusive, non-transferable internal license
to access, use and test the pre-release MuleSoft product (“Product”)
and the materials provided to Customer by MuleSoft (“Materials”)
during the term of this Agreement (“Evaluation Period”), solely
to evaluate the features, functionality and performance of the
Product. At the end of the Evaluation Period, the Product and
Materials may cease to function. The Product may not be used
for any other purpose, including but not limited to productive
or commercial use.
1.2 License Conditions.
MuleSoft retains all right, title and interest in and to the
Product and Materials, and modifications to the Product and the
Materials. Customer may not decompile, disassemble or reverse
engineer any Product. Customer may not make any copies of the
Product or Materials.  Customer may not remove or modify any
proprietary rights notices on the Products or Materials.  The
Product and Materials may not be modified, altered or enhanced.
Customer may not allow any third party to access the Product.
In no event may Customer transfer, sublicense, distribute or
run production applications on the Product. The Product may include
individual open source software components, each of which has
its own copyright and its own applicable license conditions.
The open source software is licensed to Customer under the terms
of the applicable open source license conditions and/or copyright
notices that can be found in the open_source_licenses file, the
Documentation or other materials accompanying the Software. Customer
will obtain and install all prerequisite hardware and software
(including any necessary access rights for MuleSoft) identified
by MuleSoft.
1.3 Requirements of Customer. 
Customer will be responsible for: (i) evaluating the features
of the Product, including usability, implementation, performance,
scalability, rollout; (ii) providing feedback on any additional
features requires, any functionality issues, and errors, flaws,
failures, or faults in the Product via an online MuleSoft forum;
and (iii) if jointly agreed to by the parties, participating
in press releases and marketing campaigns and acting as a reference
account.  
1.4 &quot;Confidential Information&quot;. 
means all information furnished by MuleSoft in oral, written
or machine-readable form, disclosed as a result of this Agreement,
and that should reasonably have been understood by Customer,
because of legends or other markings, the circumstances of disclosure
or the nature of the information itself, to be proprietary and
confidential to MuleSoft, an affiliate of it or to a third party.
The results of the evaluation will also be treated as MuleSoft
Confidential Information. Customer will use a reasonable standard
of care to prevent unauthorized access to or disclosure of the
Confidential Information, but in no event less than a reasonable
standard of care. Customer will disclose the Confidential Information
only to its employees with a need to know. The restrictions of
this Agreement on use and disclosure of Confidential Information
shall not apply to information that becomes publicly known through
no fault of the Customer or its personnel. All confidentiality
obligations regarding Confidential Information shall survive
with respect to any Confidential Information received prior to
the expiration or termination of this Agreement. 
1.5 Ownership. 
Customer acknowledges that MuleSoft retains ownership of all
right, title and interest to the Products and Materials and modifications
and enhancements of the foregoing.
2. Warranty Disclaimer.
2.1 MuleSoft warrants that the Product and the Materials will
be available for proper access. In the event of a breach of the
foregoing warranty, Customer’s sole remedy and MuleSoft’s sole
obligation will be to allow Customer to access the Product and
Materials from a different MuleSoft access point.   
2.2 EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY PROVIDED IN THIS AGREEMENT, THE PRODUCT
AND MATERIALS ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR
CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
NON-INFRINGEMENT, QUIET ENJOYMENT, ACCURACY OF DATA, SYSTEM INTEGRATION,
COURSE OF PERFORMANCE AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. 
MULESOFT DOES NOT GUARANTEE OR WARRANT THAT THE USE OF THE PRODUCT
OR MATERIALS WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR FREE.
3. Limitation of Liability.
IN NO EVENT WILL MULESOFT OR ITS SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY
CLAIM BASED UPON A THIRD PARTY CLAIM, ANY INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL,
SPECIAL, INDIRECT, EXEMPLARY OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, WHETHER ARISING
IN TORT, CONTRACT, OR OTHERWISE; OR FOR ANY DAMAGES ARISING OUT
OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH ANY MALFUNCTIONS, DELAYS, LOSS OF DATA,
LOST PROFITS, LOST SAVINGS, INTERRUPTION OF SERVICE, LOSS OF
BUSINESS OR ANTICIPATORY PROFITS, EVEN IF MULESOFT HAS BEEN ADVISED
OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. MULESOFT’S AGGREGATE AND
CUMULATIVE LIABILITY ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THIS AGREEMENT,
REGARDLESS OF THE FORM OF THE CAUSE OF ACTION, WHETHER IN CONTRACT,
TORT (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION NEGLIGENCE), STATUTE OR OTHERWISE
WILL BE LIMITED TO DIRECT DAMAGES AND WILL NOT EXCEED FIVE THOUSAND
DOLLARS (US $5,000). THE ALLOCATIONS OF LIABILITY IN THIS SECTION
REPRESENT THE AGREED AND BARGAINED FOR UNDERSTANDING OF THE PARTIES,
AND THE COMPENSATION OF MULESOFT FOR THE SERVICES PROVIDED HEREUNDER
REFLECTS SUCH ALLOCATIONS. THE FOREGOING LIMITATIONS, EXCLUSIONS
AND DISCLAIMERS ARE AN ALLOCATION OF THE RISK BETWEEN THE PARTIES
AND WILL APPLY TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE
LAW, EVEN IF ANY REMEDY FAILS IN ITS ESSENTIAL PURPOSE.
4. Terms and termination.
The term of this Agreement will begin and end on the dates specified
in the Evaluation Period above, when Product becomes generally
available or on the first anniversary of the Effective Date,
whichever occurs first. 
4.1 This Agreement may be terminated at any time by either party
upon written notice.  Upon termination or expiration of this
Agreement, Customer will cease using the Product and Materials.
Termination will not affect any claim, liability or right arising
prior to termination.
4.2 All rights and obligations granted under Sections 1.2, 1.4,
1.5, 2, 3, 4 and 5 of this Agreement will survive the expiration
or termination of this Agreement.  
5. General.
5.1 Independent Parties.  
Neither Customer nor MuleSoft is a legal representative, partner
or agent of the other.
5.2 Entirety.
This Agreement represents the entire agreement of the parties
with regard to the Product, Materials, and Confidential Information
and supersedes all other agreements related to this subject matter,
except for nondisclosure agreement entered into by the parties.
Delivery of an executed counterpart of this Agreement by facsimile
or any other reliable means shall be deemed to be as effective
for all purposes as delivery of the manually executed counterpart.
This Agreement may not be amended except in writing signed by
both parties.
5.3 Severability.
If any provision of this Agreement is held invalid or unenforceable
for any reason but would be valid and enforceable if appropriately
modified, then such provision will apply with the modification
necessary to make it valid and enforceable.  If such provision
cannot be so modified, the parties agree that such invalidity
will not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of the
Agreement; provided, however, that if Section 3 cannot be modified
to be valid and enforceable, this Agreement will be deemed invalid
in its entirety. 
5.4 Export.
Customer may not export or re-export the Product or Materials
except in compliance with the United States Export Administration
Act and the related rules and regulations and similar non-U.S.
government restrictions, if applicable. 
5.5 Notices.
Any notice required or permitted under the terms of this Agreement
or required by law must be in writing and must be (a) delivered
in person, (b) sent by first class registered mail, or air mail,
as appropriate, or (c) sent by overnight air courier, in each
case properly posted and fully prepaid to the appropriate address
set forth below. Either party may change its address for notice
by notice to the other party given in accordance with this Section.
Notices will be considered to have been given at the time of
actual delivery in person, five (5) business days after deposit
in the mail as set forth above, or two (2) days after delivery
to an overnight air courier service.  Notices shall be sent to:
If to MuleSoft: 
MuleSoft, Inc. 
30 Maiden Lane, Suite 500
San Francisco, CA 94108
Attn: Chief Financial Officer
If to Customer: To the Contracts Manager at Customer’s corporate
headquarters or to such other address as provided to MuleSoft
by Customer in writing.
5.6 Governing Law and Jurisdiction.
.This Agreement will be governed by and construed in accordance
with the laws of the State of New York without reference to its
conflict of laws principles. All disputes arising out of or relating
to this Agreement will be submitted to the exclusive jurisdiction
of the state or federal courts located in New York, New York,
and each party irrevocably consents to such personal jurisdiction
and waives all objections to this venue.  The parties agree that
neither the United Nations Convention on Contracts for the International
Sale of Goods nor the Uniform Computer Information Transactions
Act (UCITA) will apply in any respect to this Agreement.
   </license>

   <plugin
         id="org.mule.tooling.apikit"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.1.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.mule.tooling.apikit.deps"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.1.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
